<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<XnaContent>
  <Asset Type="DataTypes.DialogData">
    <Content>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Welcome to the world of Ensembler!</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>You will embark on a journey to become the greatest conductor and ensembler.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>But before that, you will need to learn the basics of conducting in this world.</Line>
      </Item>
      <!-- show screenshot from game manual! -->
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>During a performance, you are expected to do 3 things.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>The most important is trace: trace the flashing grey notes.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Good trace will increase your score, bad trace will decrease your score.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>In the performance interface, you will see the following things: volume, score, and combo on top of the screen.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Volume can be increased by pressing "A", and decreased by pressing "Z"</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Score shows how well you are doing in a level.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Consecutive correct moves will result in the score accumulating in an increasing rate.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Lastly, Combo shows the number of consecutive right moves you have done in the level.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Now, to the actual game play.</Line>
      </Item>
      <!-- show another screenshot from game manual! -->
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>To conduct your ensemble, simply move your baton according to the notes that appear in the screen.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Trace your baton from the initial note to the note that appears next.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>This is almost everything you need to know to play this game.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>One last thing, notice the trail of stars that follow your baton?</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>It is also an indication on how well you are doing in the level.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>While the score determines if you have passed a level, the trail of stars determines if you have failed a level.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Consecutive incorrect moves will result in decreasing the number of stars that follow your baton.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>When the number of stars reaches zero, you will have to try the level again.</Line>
      </Item>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Line>Alright, this is all you need to know about conducting in the world of Ensembler. Good luck and have fun!</Line>
      </Item>
    </Content>
    <Colors>
      <Item>
        <Character>???</Character>
        <Color>Black</Color>
      </Item>
    </Colors>
    <Faces>
    </Faces>
    <CutScenes>
    </CutScenes>
  </Asset>
</XnaContent>
